<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="product_services">
        <item>Which products and services are in your existing value proposition?</item>
        <item>Which products and services you offer help your customer to get a functional job done?</item>
        <item>Which products and services you offer help your customer to get a social job done?</item>
        <item>Which products and services you offer help your customer to get a emotional job done?</item>
        <item>Which products and services you offer help your customer to satisfy his/her basic needs?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gain_creators">
        <item>Could your products and services create positive social consequences? By making them look good or producing an increase in power or status.</item>
        <item>Could your products and services create savings that please your customers? In terms of time, money, and effort.</item>
        <item>Could your products and services outperform current value propositions and delight your customers? Regarding specific features, performance, or quality.</item>
        <item>Could your products and services fulfill a desire customers dream about? By helping them achieve their aspirations or getting relief from a hardship?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pain_relievers">
        <item>Could your products and services make your customers feel better? By killing frustrations, annoyances, and other things that give customers a headache.</item>
        <item>Could your products and services wipe out negative social consequences your customers encounter or fear? In terms of loss of face or lost power, trust, or status.</item>
        <item>Could your products and services eliminate risks your customers fear? In terms of financial, social, technical risks, or things that could potentially go wrong.</item>
        <item>Could your products and services help your customers better sleep at night? By addressing significant issues, diminishing concerns, or eliminating worries.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="customer_jobs">
        <item>What functional problems are your customers trying to solve?</item>
        <item>What emotional needs are your customers trying to satisfy?</item>
        <item>What does your customer need to accomplish that involves interaction with others?</item>
        <item>How does your customer want to feel? What does your customer need to do to feel this way?</item>
        <item>What jobs, if completed, would give the user a sense of self-satisfaction?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="customer_gains">
        <item>Which savings would make your customers happy?</item>
        <item>How do current value propositions delight your customers?</item>
        <item>What positive social consequences do your customers desire?</item>
        <item>How do your customers measure success and failure?</item>
        <item>What do customers dream about?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="customer_pains">
        <item>What makes your customers feel bad?</item>
        <item>What are their frustrations, annoyances, or things that give them a headache?</item>
        <item>What negative social consequences do your customers encounter or fear?</item>
        <item>What are their big issues, concerns, and worries?</item>
        <item>What risks do your customers fear?</item>
        <item>Are they afraid of a loss of face, power, trust, or status?</item>
        <item>Are they afraid of financial, social, or technical risks, or are they asking themselves what could go wrong?</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>